CURRICULUM VITAE

Lakhan Singh +91-9389353937, +91-9990149029 lakhan_ha@yahoo.co.in Total Exp: 7 yrs. D-43, Irshad Garden, Sahibabad, Ghaziabad-201005

WHY SHOULD YOU HIRE ME?

With 7 years of experience working as a UI/UX Designer, and Visual designer, I have worked with a variety of companies locally and internationally, designing and producing quality Web, Mobile, and print design solutions. Offering unique solutions for each client is a major strength, with effective wireframe, interactive prototype, user store, process flow, and visual design driving brand recognition as per customer requirement. As a creative thinker, I work efficiently and effectively whilst exploring options within the task at hand.

JOB RESPONSIBILITIES:-

- Create wireframes, Flow Diagrams, Interactive Prototypes, mockups, template for website Application, IOS and Android Application.
- Handling Graphic Works like Banners, Logo, Newsletters, and Brochure, Packaging work etc.
- Making business PPT for customer and management
- Improving user experience and ensuring web compatibility across all browsers and devices.
- Co-Ordinator with Developer set down all images for applications in IOS & Android Devices.
- Front-end development using HTML5 & CSS3 W3C compliance & cross-browser compatibility.
- Create Responsive website with help of bootstrap & Non-bootstrap.
- Create websites & fixing bugs.
- Gathering and evaluating user requirements from Business analytics and project manager
- Known for ability to multi-task and work on different applications at the same time.
- Ability to work with ease under pressure and strict deadlines.

WORK EXPERIENCE: -

Groupfit Technologies Pvt Ltd, Noida, UP

UI UX designer 21rd October 2019 to Till Date

Quantum Services, Noida, UP

Sr. UI UX designer
23rd October 2018 to 18th October 2019

Kay Infotech, New Delhi

Sr. Web /Graphics designer

1st June 2017 to 30th September 2018

Iglaps Technologies, Noida, UP

Web /UI Designer

1st Feb. 2014 to 31st May 2017

Wital See Marketing Limited, Gurgaon

Web /Graphics designer

1st Jan. 2012 to 31st Jan. 2014

PACL Limited, New Delhi

IT Executive

18th May. 2009 to 31st December. 2011

Using Technology and Designing Tools

- Adobe XD
- Invision
- Sketch
- Zeplin
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Coral Draw
- Dreamweaver
- Flash
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Bootstrap

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION: -

- Diploma in Multimedia (Web & Graphics) from Arena Animation
- Certificated Fast-start Usability Testing and UX Research course from Udemy.
- Certificate Mobile App Design: From Sketches to Interactive Prototypes course from Udemy.

EDUCATION:-

- MBA (IT Systems) From Vinayaka Mission University in year 2011
- B.A From M. J. P. Rohil Khand University Bareilly (U.P.) in year 2006
- Senior Secondary School From U.P. Board Allahabad in year 2003
- Higher Secondary School From U.P. Board Allahabad in year 2000

PROJECTS:

Current project: https://www.groupbima.com/

Wireframe and prototype - https://xd.adobe.com/view/5a75f9ec-21b5-433a-7456-69cdafeba8a2-2c44/

GroupBima is a customer-centric web portal which focused on offering easy and convenient insurance products as per customer requirements. GroupBima through easily accessible and digitally available

best-fit insurance solutions. And empowering people by giving them option to compare and buy the best insurance plan as per their needs.

UI/UX Projects: https://www.behance.net/lakhan_ha6435

Mobile App: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.app.projectobjects.dashboard.eni

http://bluecapitalacademy.com

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, php, Word Press, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

http://varistha.co.uk/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, .net, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

https://classyme.co.uk

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, .net, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

http://www.projects-iglaps.com/doctor/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, CodeIgniter, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

https://projects-iglaps.com/dating-site/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, CodeIgniter, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

https://broadcasthub.co.za/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, CodeIgniter, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

http://chessminds.co/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, Word Press, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

http://digitalmenu.tv/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, Word Press, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

http://erosgourmet.com/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, Word Press, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

http://www.theworldatherfeet.com/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, Word Press, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

https://bhawnayaqya.org/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, Word Press, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

https://www.winkleightimber.co.uk/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, Magneto, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

https://www.galaxysports.co.uk/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, Html, CSS, jQuery And JavaScript, .net

https://www.easycoupondeal.com/

Using tool: Adobe Photoshop, CodeIgniter, Bootstrap, CSS, Html, jQuery And JavaScript

PERSONAL DETAILS:-			
Name	:	Lakhan Singh	
Father Name	:	Shri Tirmal Singh	
Date of Birth	:	25th Feb. 1984	
Condon		Mala	

Gender : Male

Marital States : Married

Nationality : Indian

Language Knowledge : Hindi, English
Hobbies : Listening Music
Strength : Self Confidence

Mobile Number : +91-9389353937, +91-9990149029

Declaration:

I hereby declare that information given above, are correct as per best of my knowledge.

Date:	(Lakhan S	Singh)
Place:		